





Goal-oriented Full-Stack Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support. Proficient in strategic and tactical planning, and client relationship management (CRM).

Skilled in the following:

Languages: HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, EJS. Framework: Express.js, React.js, jQuery.

Technologies: Wordpress, Bootstrap 4, Hyper, Linux, Git, Postman, Heroku, Agile, Salesforce, Atom.

Database: NPM, SQL, Microsoft SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Firebase.

Design Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Freelance | Miami, FL | March 2020 - Present

- Develop highly visible responsive WordPress websites based on delivered requirements and design.
- Used various technologies to make code repairs and optimize corporate website.
- Perform and direct website updates.
- Tested websites and performed troubleshooting prior to deployment.
- Analyzed requirements and designed, developed and implemented software applications for multiple websites.
- Design, build, and maintain websites, using authoring and scripting languages, content creation tools, management tools, and digital media.
- Write, design, and edit web page content, and work with others producing content.
- Evaluate code to ensure that it is valid, is properly structured, meets industry standards and is compatible with browsers, devices, or operating systems.
- Analyze user needs to determine technical requirements.
- Renew domain name registrations.
- Develop databases that support web applications and web sites.
- Write supporting code for web applications or websites.
- Design and implement web site security measures such as firewalls or message encryption.
- Select programming languages, design tools, or applications.
- Recommend and implement performance improvements.

Logistics Operations Manager

Dover Jewelry and Diamonds | Miami, FL | September 2018 - March 2020

- · Provide assistance for customers with special billing requests
- Troubleshooting issues and problem solving with speed and efficiency
- Monitor inventory levels and requisition or purchase supplies as needed
- Develop or update procedures, policies, or standards
- Determine charges for services requested, collect deposits and payments, and arrange for billing
- Arrange for necessary maintenance and repair work
- Check to ensure that appropriate changes were made to resolve customers' problems
- Use performance improvement techniques to continually improve logistics services for customers
- Processed 300 invoices each week and mailed documentation to clients

Product/Interface Designer

Freelance | Miami, FL | May 2012 - March 2020

- Acted as a liaison between technology team, customers and subject matter experts to establish requirements and determine user needs.
- Defined navigation, user workflows and layouts focusing on usability.
- Developed wireframes, interface mockups and page prototypes.
- Planned and executed usability testing, incorporated user feedback into final product design.
- Produced graphic user interfaces for desktop browsers, tablet and mobile devices.

EDUCATION

August 2015 - June 2020

Florida International University, Miami - B.A. Communication & Media

August 2012 - June 2015

Miami Dade College, Miami - A.A. Graphic Arts

June 2020 - September 2020

The App Brewery, Udemy - The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp

LINKS



